[ar: Lyn]
[ti: Wake Up, Get Up, Get Out There]
[al: Persona 20th Anniversary All Time Best Album]
[by: adhan]
[length: 01:36]
[id: zppwqaci]
[00:00.00]
[00:29.33]Who am I?
[00:31.70]Am I not unique?
[00:33.89]Maybe I'm not here at all
[00:37.02]Look, the fakers
[00:39.02]Blinding us with lies
[00:41.45]The breakers of us all
[00:44.45]
[00:44.70]Oh, it's useless
[00:48.39]What could it mean that we're here?
[00:51.64]Can we make a difference
[00:56.08]If we don't break outta here?
[00:57.58]
[00:59.02]Wake up, get up, get out there
[01:02.27]Raise your voice against liars
[01:06.83]Feed your anger like fire
[01:09.39]Why does nobody want change?
[01:13.70]
[01:14.02]Just imagine you're out there
[01:17.08]Swatting lies in the making
[01:21.39]Can't move fast without breaking
[01:24.52]If you hold on life won't change
[01:29.27]
[02:46.08]The fakers
[02:47.70]Are all sick at heart
[02:49.89]Their faces hiding their fear
[02:52.83]They look down on
[02:55.27]All the rest of us
[02:57.52]Like they're some special breed
[03:00.27]
[03:00.83]Who's the high lord
[03:04.52]Who thinks he's better than us?
[03:08.02]Ain't it a crime, that?
[03:12.08]Is there a mission for us?
[03:14.08]
[03:15.95]Who is that high lord?
[03:19.83]Who'd kill a million of us?
[03:23.33]And as the bell tolls
[03:26.83]Is there no remission for us?
[03:29.52]
[03:30.33]Wake up, get up, get out there
[03:33.39]There's more to life than their way
[03:37.83]If you'd live you cannot stay
[03:40.45]Why does nobody want change?
[03:44.58]
[03:45.20]Let your voices ring out, yeah
[03:49.20]Take the mask off and be free
[03:53.08]Find yourself in the debris
[03:55.89]If you hold on life won't change
[04:00.95]Wake up, get up, get out there
[04:01.33]
[04:04.38]Raise your voice against liars
[04:08.26]Feed your anger like fire
[04:11.32]Why does nobody want change?
[04:15.32]
[04:16.07]Just imagine you're out there
[04:19.82]Swatting lies in the making
[04:23.13]Can't move fast without breaking
[04:26.51]If you hold on life won't change 
[04:29.50]