[ar: Silent Siren]
[ti: DanceMusiQ]
[al: サイレントサイレン]
[by: riuz14]
[length: 04:08]
[id: nlowwhca]
[00:01.17]
[00:06.54]Wao <00:07.40>Wao <00:08.14>Dancing
[00:09.23]Artist: Silent Siren
[00:11.91]Wao <00:13.02>Wao <00:13.71>Dancing
[00:14.37]Title: DanceMusiQ
[00:17.68]Wao <00:18.59>Wao <00:19.33>Dancing
[00:20.18]Album: サイレントサイレン
[00:23.56]Wao <00:24.14>Wao <00:24.89>Dancing
[00:25.85]LRC: RIUZ14
[00:28.28]
[00:29.10]Miraa <00:29.67>booru <00:30.11>sakkaku <00:30.80>saseru <00:31.11>yo <00:31.36>ni <00:31.68>gira <00:32.05>tsuku <00:32.61>mayonaka <00:33.11>no <00:33.54>party
[00:34.24]Kurayami <00:35.35>ni <00:35.62>magirete <00:36.36>konareta <00:36.86>tetsuki <00:37.43>atashi <00:37.92>wo <00:38.30>yuuwaku <00:38.80>shiteru
[00:39.87]Machi <00:40.73>wa <00:41.17>neon <00:41.73>ni <00:42.11>nomare <00:42.42>hoshi <00:42.98>hitotsu <00:43.37>sura <00:43.87>mienaku <00:44.36>natte
[00:45.50]Rasen <00:45.98>wo <00:46.41>egaita <00:46.86>you <00:47.17>ni <00:47.66>narenai <00:48.35>joukyou <00:49.23>kai <00:49.54>kugutteiru <00:50.17>no
[00:50.80]
[00:50.96]Namerareta <00:52.75>mon <00:53.07>ne <00:53.82>koshi <00:54.31>ni <00:54.82>mawasu <00:55.38>te <00:55.70>oi <00:56.01>harai
[00:56.37]Chotto <00:57.79>hoka <00:58.22>no <00:58.66>ko <00:58.97>to <00:59.41>isshoni <01:00.03>shinaide
[01:01.06]
[01:01.33]Hage<01:02.09>shi<01:02.63>ku
[01:04.15]Yure <01:04.84>ku<01:05.44>ruu
[01:06.88]Dansu <01:07.59>furo<01:08.13>a
[01:09.70]O<01:10.09>do<01:10.83>tte
[01:13.18]Na <01:13.58>Na <01:13.97>Na <01:14.54>Na <01:14.84>Na <01:15.15>Na
[01:15.92](Na <01:16.40>Na <01:16.77>Na <01:17.34>Na <01:17.66>Na <01:17.96>Na)
[01:18.73]Na <01:19.07>Na <01:19.50>Na <01:20.01>Na <01:20.45>Na <01:20.76>Na
[01:21.36](Na <01:21.95>Na <01:22.32>Na <01:22.88>Na <01:23.25>Na <01:23.56>Na)
[01:23.61]Tomarana<01:24.19>ide
[01:24.86]
[01:36.05]Ura <01:36.38>utsu <01:37.07>biito <01:37.89>shigekiteki <01:38.57>sugiru <01:39.20>mayonaka <01:40.07>no <01:40.45>Lonely
[01:41.30]Kurayami <01:42.45>ni <01:42.89>magirete <01:43.50>konareta <01:44.01>tetsuki <01:44.39>mina <01:45.07>koshi <01:45.45>wo <01:45.82>futteru <01:46.13>no
[01:47.11]Machi <01:47.68>wa <01:47.99>neon <01:48.62>ni <01:49.12>yuragi <01:49.56>tsuki <01:49.87>akari <01:50.24>sura <01:50.62>mienaku <01:51.49>natte
[01:52.42]Rasen <01:52.97>wo <01:53.47>egaita <01:53.90>you <01:54.22>ni <01:54.65>narenai <01:55.03>haihiiru <01:56.33>oto <01:56.69>hibikaseteru <01:57.01>no
[01:57.80]
[01:58.29]Namerareta <01:59.67>mon <01:59.99>ne <02:00.73>kata <02:01.30>ni <02:01.73>mawasu <02:02.17>te <02:02.48>oi <02:02.80>harai
[02:03.23]Chotto <02:04.61>hoka <02:05.17>no <02:05.61>ko <02:05.92>to <02:06.37>isshoni <02:06.86>shinaide
[02:07.88]
[02:08.44]Hage<02:08.99>shiku
[02:11.08]Yure <02:11.67>kuruu
[02:13.70]Dansu <02:14.37>furoa
[02:16.64]Odo<02:17.92>tte
[02:20.07]Na <02:20.54>Na <02:20.92>Na <02:21.48>Na <02:21.86>Na <02:22.17>Na
[02:22.81](Na <02:23.35>Na <02:23.74>Na <02:24.30>Na <02:24.67>Na <02:24.97>Na)
[02:25.88]Na <02:26.10>Na <02:26.49>Na <02:27.05>Na <02:27.41>Na <02:27.73>Na
[02:28.32](Na <02:28.93>Na <02:29.23>Na <02:29.79>Na <02:30.17>Na <02:30.48>Na)
[02:30.56]Owarana<02:31.29>ide
[02:31.93]
[03:04.28]Yasashiku <03:06.89>oshiete <03:09.71>dansu <03:10.53>furoa <03:12.53>odo<03:13.78>tte
[03:14.83]
[03:15.34]Hage<03:15.96>shiku
[03:18.00]Yure <03:18.58>kuruu
[03:20.80]Dansu <03:21.41>furoa
[03:23.69]Odo<03:24.65>tte
[03:27.02]Na <03:27.46>Na <03:27.84>Na <03:28.46>Na <03:28.84>Na <03:29.09>Na
[03:29.72](Na <03:30.34>Na <03:30.65>Na <03:31.15>Na <03:31.52>Na <03:31.96>Na)
[03:32.59]Na <03:33.09>Na <03:33.46>Na <03:33.90>Na <03:34.28>Na <03:34.58>Na
[03:35.34](Na <03:35.77>Na <03:36.15>Na <03:36.72>Na <03:37.02>Na <03:37.34>Na)
[03:37.41]Tomarana<03:38.28>ide
[03:38.72]
[03:40.34]RIUZ14