[ar: Dia Frampton]
[ti: Billy The Kid]
[al: Red]

[00:00.00]
[00:26.74]Now once upon a time when the West was old
[00:30.24]A ma saw her son was a sight to behold
[00:33.87]He could shoot his daddy's gun like a straight arrow
[00:37.61]He wrestled with the rattlesnakes before he walked
[00:42.12]Ya, he grew up fast with a hardened grit
[00:45.36]And he had the pluck and he had the wit
[00:49.24]Ya his mamma called him William till he up and quit
[00:53.36]And in these here parts he's known as Billy the Kid

[00:57.62]I've had you in my sights, my arms for so long.
[01:02.30]Where did you go? I didn't know.
[01:05.74]I've been around here waiting for so long, so long
[01:10.46]And I'll wait for you.

[01:20.77]He was as tough as nails, barging in the saloon
[01:24.21]Missing an eye, gun glowed in the moon
[01:28.03]He called out to the crowd, "I don't want no fuss.
[01:31.78]See, I'm looking for a runaway, who looks like this!"
[01:35.33]And he slammed the paper down, it was covered in dust,
[01:39.71]But the crowd kept silent, sure, he looked real tough,
[01:43.58]But they knew the portrait well, and they knew not to,
[01:47.52]Mess with Billy the Kid and his gang of thugs

[01:51.96]I've had you in my sights, my arms for so long.
[01:56.56]Where did you go? I didn't know.
[01:59.86]I've been around here waiting for so long, so long
[02:04.80]And I'll wait for you.

[02:07.70]I've had you in my sights, my arms for so long.
[02:11.88]Where did you go? I didn't know.
[02:15.19]I've been around here waiting for so long, so long
[02:20.44]And I'll wait for you.

[02:22.72]The sheriff knocked on the door of a pretty girl
[02:26.15]Tipped his hat, said, "We gotta have a look around.
[02:29.84]We'll give you cash if you tip off the fugitive."
[02:33.65]She bit her lip, she was in love and acted clueless.
[02:36.91]He grabbed her arm and said, "We heard you been a harborin'.
[02:41.22]Give him up, I give my word I'll keep your name clean."
[02:45.40]She steered 'em clear of the cracks in the floorboards and
[02:49.22]Said, "You'll never find him, you'll never find him!"

[02:53.97]I've had you in my sights, my arms for so long.
[02:58.41]Where did you go? I didn't know.
[03:01.78]I've been around here waiting for so long, so long
[03:06.91]And I'll wait for you.

[03:09.47]I've had you in my sights, my arms for so long.
[03:13.83]Where did you go? I didn't know.
[03:17.06]I've been around here waiting for so long, so long
[03:22.37]And I'll wait for you.
