[ar: Dido]
[ti: This Land Is Mine]
[al: Life For Rent]
[by: van]
[offset: 500]
[id: tk_wqhili]
[00:15.79]
[00:17.79]From behind these walls I hear your song
[00:23.59]Oh, sweet words
[00:26.19]The music that you play lights up my world
[00:31.86]The sweetest that I've heard
[00:34.85]Could it be that I've been touched and turned
[00:40.37]Oh Lord, please finally…finally things are changing
[00:48.21]
[00:49.85]This land is mine but I'll let you rule
[00:54.13]I let you navigate and demand
[00:58.46]Just as long as you know…this land is mine
[01:06.65]So find your home and settle in
[01:11.09]Ohhh, I'm ready to let you in
[01:15.47]Just as long as we know…this land is mine
[01:21.60]
[01:25.40]After all the battles and the wars
[01:31.10]The scars and loss
[01:33.96]I'm still the queen of my domain
[01:39.51]and feeling stronger now
[01:42.30]The walls are down a little more each day
[01:48.11]Since you came, finally…finally things are changing
[01:56.36]
[01:57.51]This land is mine but I'll let you rule
[02:01.83]I let you navigate and demand
[02:06.08]Just as long as you know…this land is mine
[02:14.35]So find your home and settle in
[02:18.75]Ohhh, I'm ready to let you in
[02:23.00]Just as long as we know…this land is mine
[02:29.25]
[02:32.52]Follow the days I've travelled alone
[02:39.84]In this cold and colorless place till now
[02:49.44]It's what I had to pay
[02:52.39]This land is mine but I'll let you rule
[02:56.71]I let you navigate and demand
[03:01.05]Just as long as you know…this land is mine
[03:09.26]So find your home and settle in
[03:13.73]Ohhh, I'm ready to let you in
[03:17.99]Just as long as we know…this land is mine
[03:24.34]
[03:26.33]This land is mine and I let you rule
[03:30.53]I let you navigate and demand
[03:34.79]Just as long as you know…this land is mine
[03:41.21]
[03:42.69]
[03:44.30]END
