[ar: ATB feat. Tiff Lacey]
[ti: My Everything]
[al: Future Memories]
[by: RevolutionVoid]
[length: 05:04]
[re: RhythmiKaRuTTE_Spectro]
[ve: 2021-10-20]
[00:02.86]You are[00:05.07]
[00:14.50]You are all I'll ever need[00:20.78]
[00:22.83]You're my everything[00:24.68]
[01:18.14]I wanna thank you, for not giving up on me
[01:23.98]I wanna thank you, for believing what could be
[01:32.60]You see it means so very much to me[01:38.59]
[01:41.29]I wanna thank you, for never letting go
[01:47.07]I wanna thank you, for waiting in the cold
[01:53.36]I don't think you realise, how could you know?
[01:59.23]You are everything to me, oh you are[02:08.39]
[02:10.82]You are all I'll ever need[02:16.87]
[02:19.27]You're my everything[02:21.63]
[02:51.08]I wanna tell you, but words fail me at this time
[02:56.99]I wanna tell you, that you're always on my mind
[03:05.82]From the moment that I wake, to last thing at night[03:11.74]
[03:14.27]I wanna show you, this love is deep inside
[03:20.14]I wanna show you, you see it in my eyes
[03:26.77]Have you sensed the change in me, do you realise?
[03:32.33]You are everything to me, oh you are[03:41.43]
[03:44.00]You are all I'll ever need[03:50.09]
[03:52.30]You're my everything[03:54.10]
[03:55.56]You are everything to me, oh you are[04:04.66]
[04:07.18]You are all I'll ever need[04:13.30]
[04:15.53]You're my everything[04:17.28]
[04:42.05]You are[04:44.41]
[04:53.61]You are all I'll ever need[05:00.08]
[05:02.05]You're my everything[05:03.91]