[ar: BT feat. Jes]
[ti: Every Other Way (Armin van Buuren Remix)]
[by: Trajade]
[id: js_ivqshnsh]
[00:00.00]
[02:19.17]Is it strained, when I call you
[02:26.26]Or do you think, that I might forget
[02:33.48]I wish I could run, to you when you need me
[02:40.67]You know I can't be far
[02:45.28]For long
[02:50.48]
[03:48.19]Heart don't fail me now
[03:52.69]Cause there is no time to waste
[03:56.10]Don't shut me out, we shouldn't wait another day
[04:03.30]I've searched for you, on my hearts high speed chase
[04:10.90]Hear me out, may be the only chance to say
[04:18.29]Hold me now
[04:22.50]I've said it Every Other Way
[04:24.90]
[04:33.34]Hold me now
[04:37.24]I've said it Every Other Way
[04:40.04]
[06:07.35]Heart don't fail me now
[06:12.25]Cause there is no time to waste
[06:15.45]Don't shut me out, we shouldn't wait another day
[06:22.65]I've searched for you, on my hearts high speed chase
[06:30.15]Hear me out, may be the only chance to say
[06:37.85]Hear me out, may be the only chance to say
[06:45.15]Hold me now
[06:48.94]I've said it Every Other Way
[06:51.75]
