[ar: Tiësto feat. JES]
[ti: Everything (Andrew Bennett Remix)]
[al: Magikal Journey (The Hits Collection 1998-2008)]
[by: RevolutionVoid]
[length: 06:01]
[00:00.00]
[01:11.25]How breathless I feel in your arms
[01:18.30]How breathless you make me feel so
[01:25.53]There's no one before in my eyes
[01:32.57]I take what you give me
[01:36.75]
[01:40.37]Everything sounds better
[01:44.09]
[01:47.42]Everything looks brighter
[01:51.31]
[01:54.54]Everything
[01:56.08]
[02:01.73]Everything (feels better)
[02:05.33]
[02:08.78]Everything sounds better
[02:12.51]
[02:15.82]Everything looks brighter
[02:19.75]
[02:23.05]Everything tastes better
[02:26.96]
[02:29.31]Everything you do feels better
[02:32.96]
[02:39.51](Sounds better)
[02:41.25]
[04:16.84]Everything sounds better
[04:23.83]Everything looks brighter (looks brighter)
[04:30.79]And everything tastes better (tastes better)
[04:38.01]Everything feels better
[04:41.94]
