[ar: Regina Spektor]
[ti: Raindrops]
[id: kv_bowcblqb]

[00:14.37]You don’t know but that’s okay
[00:19.03]You might find me anyway
[00:22.40]Don’t you know that i
[00:23.96]Belong arm in arm with you, baby
[00:30.32]In a town that’s cold and gray
[00:33.47]We will have a sunny day
[00:37.08]Don’t you know that i
[00:38.22]Belong arm in arm with you, baby…
[00:47.83]I do not know
[00:49.31]Where does it go
[00:50.31]When it goes
[00:53.37]Suddenly though
[00:55.41]Everything’s slow
[00:56.34]And i miss you so
[01:01.59]Round each corner there’s a chance
[01:04.87]People searching glance to glance
[01:08.33]Moving bout real fast
[01:09.95]Like insects and fish when they’re scared
[01:15.75]And they sing the same old song
[01:19.37]Though it’s been so very long
[01:22.21]They sing, raindrops falling on my head
[01:25.99]But that doesn’t mean that i am dead
[01:29.91]And i do not know
[01:31.44]Where does it go
[01:32.49]When it goes
[01:35.62]Suddenly though
[01:37.37]Everything’s slow
[01:38.76]And i miss you so
[01:44.69]You don’t know but that’s okay
[01:47.63]You might find me anyway

[01:51.24]Don’t you know that i
[01:52.99]Belong arm in arm with you, baby
[01:58.71]In a town that’s cold and gray
[02:01.79]We will have a sunny day
[02:05.66]Don’t you know that i

[02:07.73]Belong arm in arm with you, baby…
