[ar: Regina Spektor]
[ti: Fidelity]
[al: Begin to Hope]
[by: RevolutionVoid]
[length: 03:46]
[id: og_pwozqkqi]
[00:00.20](Shake it up)[00:00.65]
[00:07.05]I never loved nobody fully
[00:12.30]Always one foot on the ground
[00:17.68]And by protecting my heart truly
[00:21.41]I got lost in the sounds
[00:26.11]I hear in my mind
[00:28.96]All these voices
[00:31.22]I hear in my mind all these words
[00:36.36]I hear in my mind all this music
[00:41.60]And it breaks my heart
[00:43.88]And it breaks my heart
[00:46.58]And it breaks my heart
[00:51.57]It breaks my heart
[00:58.46]And suppose I never ever met you
[01:03.50]Suppose we never fell in love
[01:08.37]Suppose I never ever let you kiss me so sweet and so soft
[01:18.88]Suppose I never ever saw you
[01:24.21]Suppose we never ever called
[01:29.02]Suppose I kept on singing love songs just to break my own fall
[01:37.49]Just to break my fall
[01:42.36]Just to break my fall
[01:47.76]Just to break my fall
[01:52.97]Break my fall
[01:55.52]Break my fall
[01:58.75]All my friends say that of course its gonna get better
[02:02.60]Gonna get better
[02:03.90]Better better better better
[02:05.21]Better better better
[02:11.62]I never love nobody fully
[02:16.06]Always one foot on the ground
[02:21.04]And by protecting my heart truly
[02:25.15]I got lost
[02:27.68]In the sounds
[02:30.00]I hear in my mind
[02:32.58]All these voices
[02:34.90]I hear in my mind all these words
[02:39.89]I hear in my mind
[02:42.83]All this music
[02:45.25]And it breaks my heart
[02:47.64]It breaks my heart
[02:50.92]I hear in my mind
[02:53.11]All these voices
[02:55.32]I hear in my mind all these words
[03:00.52]I hear in my mind
[03:03.20]All this music
[03:05.77]And it breaks my heart
[03:07.95]It breaks my heart
[03:10.99]Breaks my
[03:11.68]Heart
[03:16.06]Breaks my heart
[03:20.81]and it breaks my heart
[03:25.99]it breaks my heart
[03:28.29]and it breaks my heart
[03:31.38]and it breaks my heart[03:38.73]